Register of the Edward Eyre Hunt Papers, 1902-1953
Hoover Institution Archives
Edward Eyre Hunt Papers,
1902-1953
56008
Hunt, Edward E., 1885-1953
104 manuscript boxes, 2 oversize boxes, 1 envelope, 3 maps. (44.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Reports, memoranda, correspondence, diaries, writings, printed matter, and photographs, relating to relief and reconstruction in Europe during and after World Wars I and II (especially in Belgium, France, Germany, Italy, and Poland), the Commission for Relief in Belgium, the American Red Cross, Herbert Hoover and the presidential campaign of 1920, and American economic conditions between the two world wars.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Access Points
Hoover, Herbert, 1874-1964.; American National Red Cross.; Commission for Relief in Belgium (1914-1930); United Nations Relief and Rehabilitation Administration.; United States. President's Emergency Committee for Employment.; International relief.; Presidents--United States--Election--1920.; Reconstruction (1914-1939); Reconstruction (1939-1951); Unemployed--United States.; World War, 1914-1918.; World War, 1914-1918--Belgium.; World War, 1914-1918--Civilian relief.; World War, 1939-1945.; World War, 1939-1945--Civilian relief.; World War, 1939-1945--Economic aspects.; Belgium.; United States--Foreign relations.; United States--Economic conditions.; United States--Politics and government.; Economists.
Biographical Notes
1885, August 1 Born, Bellwood, Nebraska
1910 A.B., Harvard
1910 Author, Sir Orfeo
1910-1912 Secretary for appointments and assistant in English Department, Harvard
1912-1914 Editorial staff, American Magazine, New York
1914 War Correspondent, Europe
1914-1916 American delegate, Commission for Relief in Belgium in charge of Province of Antwerp
1916 Author, War Bread: A Personal Narrative of the War and Relief in Belgium
1916 Author, Haj
1917 Director of Publications, American Red Cross, Washington, D.C.
1917-1918 Head of Economic Rehabilitation work of Red Cross in France
1917 Director General of Civilian Relief, Red Cross, Italy
1918 Author, Tales from a Famished Land
1918 Author, The Red Cross on the Front Line in the Great Battle of 1918
1920 Labor Manager, Clothing Industry, New York
1920 Appointed by Herbert Hoover as member of the Committee on Elimination of Waste in Industry, Federated American Engineering Societies
1921 Secretary of Conference on Unemployment called by President Warren Harding
1921 Co-author, Waste in Industry
1922-1923 Secretary, U.S. Coal Commission
1923 Co-author, Business Cycles and Unemployment
1924 Co-author, Seasonal Operation in the Construction Industries
1924 Editor, Scientific Management Since Taylor
1925 Author, Conferences, Committees, Conventions, and How to Run Them
1925 Editor, What the Coal Commission Found
1927 American Expert on Scientific Management, League of Nations, World Economic Conference
1928 Member, Committee on Recent Economic Changes
1929 Editor, Recent Economic Changes in the United States
1930 Author, An Audit of America
1930-1931 Secretary, President's Emergency Committee for Employment
1930-1933 Member, President's Research Committee on Social Trends
1931 American member of World Economic Depression Inquiry
1937 Author, Greathouse
1939-1940 Engaged in economic and social surveys, Venezuela
1942-1943 Chief Industrial Economist, War Production Board
1943 Associate Director, Field Operations, Office of Foreign Relief and Rehabilitation, U.S. Department of State
1944 Chief of Italian Division, Foreign Economic Administration
1944 Editor, The Power Industry and the Public Interest
1945-1946 Director, Italian Division, U.S. Department of State
Series Description
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1946 (Box 1-8)
  Arranged alphabetically by name of correspondent.
- SUBJECT FILE, 1914-1946 (Box 9-54)
  Reports, memoranda, printed material, correspondence, arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
- SPEECHES AND WRITINGS, 1921-1945 (Box 55-62)
  Handwritten and typewritten manuscripts and drafts of books, speeches and articles by Edward E. Hunt, arranged alphabetically by title or subject.
- AUDIO-VISUAL.
  See photo card catalog.
Container List
- CORRESPONDENCE, 1919-1946
  - General, 1931-1945 (Box 1)
  - Unidentified, 1930-1935
  - Abell, Earle I., 1945
  - Acheson, Dean, 1944-1945
  - Adams, Quincy, 1942
  - Adams, Samuel G., 1946
  - Adams, Warren, 1942
  - Adler, Laurence, 1943-1944
  - A'Hearn, L. W., 1944-1945
  - Alderson, Wroe, 1942-1943
  - Aldred, J. E., 1944
  - Alexander, Will W., 1943
  - Aley, Maxwell, 1943
  - Allbaugh, L. G., 1944-1945
  - Allen, Carolyn E., 1930-1934
  - Allen, Mrs. Francis K., 1943
  - Allen, G. F., 1943-1944
  - Altschul, Eugene, 1942
  - American Society of Mechanical Engineers, 1929-1930
  - Andersen, Edythe V., 1943
  - Anderson, Dewey, 1943-1944
  - Anderson, Paul B., 1944
  - Andrews, Joseph A., 1945
  - Angell, James W., 1944
  - Antolini, A. G., 1943-1944
  - Applebee, Francis, 1943
  - Appleby, Paul, 1942
  - Arai, Yoneo, 1946
  - Archer, George, 1942
  - Archer, Laird, 1943-1944
  - Armstrong, Ian, 1945
  - Armstrong, Maj. T. P., 1942-1943
  - Arpan, Floyd G., 1942
  - Ascoli, Max, 1946
  - Atkinson, Geoffrey, 1943
  - Austen, David E., 1946
  - Austin, Mrs. C. B., 1943
  - Austin, Lt. Col. Jason McVay, 1943
  - Bailey, Samuel R., 1942
  - Baille, Mrs. Helen Tufts, 1943
  - Baker, Christina H., n.d.
  - Baker, Mrs. George Pierce, 1943
  - Baker, Newcombe C., 1945
  - Baldanzi, George, 1944
  - Baldwin and Mermey, 1944-1945
  - Baldwin, C. B., 1943
  - Baldwin Locomotive Works, 1944
  - Baldwin Ray, 1944
  - Baldwin, Roger, 1942
  - Bane, Suda L., 1934-1944
  - Barbato, Guy, 1944
  - Barbieri, Cesare, 1945
  - Barms, J. S., 1943
  - Barner, Blakeslee, 1944-1945
  - Barovetto, Silvio L., 1945
  - Barrett, Frank A., 1943
  - Bary, Constantine, 1942
  - Barzilai, Gemma, 1945
  - Bassie, Lewis, 1942
  - Bateson, Gregory, 1943
  - Baumgardner, Anne, 1943
  - Beebe, S. K., 1944
  - Belknap, Mrs. Carroll, 1942-1944
  - Bell, Claude C., 1933
  - Bell, John, 1942
  - Belmont, George L., 1945
  - Bement, Alon, 1942
  - Bennett, M. K., 1943-1944
  - Berriman, William, 1944
  - Bevan, Arthur, 1944
  - Bingham, Walter V., 1942-1944
  - Blackly, Louis, 1945
  - Blaisdell, Thomas C., Jr., 1942-1946
  - Blanchard, Fred M., 1944
  - Blandford, John B., Jr., 1942
  - Blau, Clarence, 1944
  - Bleick, Edgar C., 1944
  - Bohn, Frank, 1944
  - Bonnell, Allen T., 1943
  - Bouchard, George, 1943
  - Boudreau, Frank, 1942
  - Bovard, Alice M., 1943
  - Brandeis, Irma, 1943
  - Brecht, Arnold, 1942
  - Brenner, Ann Reed, 1936
  - Bricca, John Francis, 1944
  - Britt, Steuart H., 1942
  - Brown, C. Edgar, 1945
  - Brown, Nelson C., 1945-1946
  - Brown, Percy S., 1942
  - Browne, Gilbert G., 1934
  - Brunot, James, 1944-1945
  - Buck, Nina B., 1934
  - Bullard, Arthur, 1934
  - Burgess, E. W., 1943
  - Burns, Norman, 1943
  - Cabot, Philip, 1922 (Box 2)
  - California Economic Research Council, 1932
  - Calkins, Hugh, 1943
  - Cameron, Lt. Col. Ward M., 1945
  - Campbell, A. Bruce, 1945
  - Canepa, Avv. Antonio, 1945
  - Capital Transit Company, 1942
  - Carlucci, Leo, 1943
  - Carsel, Wilfred, 1944
  - Carson, William J., 1944
  - Carstens, Arthur, 1944
  - Carter, A. Aileen, 1944
  - Cassels, John, 1942-1945
  - Castle, Helen H., 1945
  - Cates, L., 1942
  - Cerruti and Cominelli, 1944
  - Chamberlain, Joseph B., 1944-1946
  - Chase, Fred H., 1944
  - Chatwood, Edward, 1943-1944
  - Chatwood, Millard, 1944
  - Christen, L. H., 1945-1946
  - Cigonani, A. G., 1945
  - Clapp, Paul S., 1944
  - Clark, Evans, 1943-1944
  - Clark, Victor S., 1942
  - Clark, Wallace, 1943
  - Clark, William M., Jr., 1944
  - Cleveland, Harlan, 1943-1946
  - Coates, Gerald, 1945
  - Cochrell, C. F., 1928
  - Coe, Frank, 1943-1946
  - Coffin, R. T. P., 1944
  - Cohen, Wally, 1944
  - Cole, Maj. S. J., 1942
  - Conant, James Bryant, 1943
  - Connell, Mrs. Richard, 1944
  - Constantine, Earl, 1942
  - Contini, Paolo, 1945
  - Cooke, Morris L., 1928-1944
  - Coolidge, President Calvin, 1924
  - Coolidge, Harold J., Jr., 1943
  - Copeland, Morris, 1942
  - Corrigan, Frank P., 1943-1945
  - Cosmos Club, 1942-1944
  - Cover, John, 1942-1943
  - Cowan, David, 1943
  - Cowell, Charles C., 1943
  - Cox, Oscar, 1945-1946
  - Crawford, David, 1935
  - Crellin, Curtis V., 1944
  - Crosetto, Michael G., 1945
  - Cuccomarino, Carlo, 1945
  - Culbertson, Mrs. T. M., 1945
  - Currie, Laughlin, 1945-1946
  - Dall, Marcus, 1943
  - Danielsan, N. R., 1944
  - D'Arienzo, Franco V., 1944
  - Darlington, Charles, 1942-1943
  - Davies, Clarence, 1944
  - Davis, Dwight F., 1942
  - Davis, Col. J. C., 1945
  - Davis, Joseph S., 1943
  - Davis, Norman H., 1942
  - Day, Edmund E., 1934
  - Dayton, Kenneth, 1943
  - Deal, E. L., 1945
  - Dean, Edward C., 1944
  - Dean, V. M., 1943
  - DeRosa, Michelangelo, 1944
  - DeSager, W. A., 1944
  - Devlin, Edmund J., 1929-1934
  - Dewart, F. W., 1945
  - Dewey, Edward R., 1942
  - Dewhurst, J. Frederic, 1942-1945
  - Dickinson, Catherine, 1934-1942
  - Dietrich, Ethel B., 1944
  - Dillencourt, J. B., 1943
  - Dinwiddie, Courtenay, 1934
  - Dirkson, Everett M., 1945
  - Dixon, P. H., 1942
  - Dodd, E. Merrick, 1935
  - Domeratzky, Louis, 1934
  - Dominick, Mrs. William F., 1935
  - Dorgin, A. L., 1945
  - Dort, Dallas, 1944-1945
  - Douglas, James H., Jr., 1946
  - Douglas, Richard, 1943
  - Dowling, Walter C., 1946
  - Doyle, Henry Grattan, 1943
  - Dudley, John G., 1933-1934
  - Dunn, Clyde, n.d.
  - Eakins, Martha St. John, 1937
  - Eastman, Lucius R., 1930-1942
  - Eaton, Amy, 1945
  - Edgerton, Maj. Gen. Glen E., n.d.
  - Ehlers, Mrs. E. G., 1945
  - Eliot, Charles, 1942-1944
  - Ellis, John H., 1943
  - Emerson, Rupert, 1944-1945
  - English, Maurice, 1945
  - Englund, Eric, 1944-1945
  - Epstein, Ralph C., 1932
  - Ericsson, Marjory, 1944
  - Errante, Guido, 1944
  - Erwin, Thomas, 1942
  - Estes, L. D., 1946
  - Evarts, Richard G., 1944
  - Facci, Joseph E., 1944 (Box 3)
  - Fahy, Charles, 1944
  - Fairchild, David, 1943
  - Faraone, Frederick, 1945
  - Feiker, Frederick M., 1934
  - Field, G. Lowell, 1944
  - Field, Louise, 1943-1944
  - Filbert, R. B., 1944
  - Fisher, Boyd, 1943
  - Fisher, H. H., 1933-1943
  - Fitzgerald, D. A., 1942
  - Fitzpatrick, F. Stewart, 1942
  - Flanders, Ralph E., 1935
  - Fleming, Harold, 1942
  - Fleming, John, 1943
  - Fleming, Maj. Gen. Philip, 1945
  - Flesh, Edward M., 1943
  - Foley, Col. Edward H., Jr., 1946
  - Forman, Henry James, 1943
  - Forrest, Lt. Col. Maulesby, 1945
  - Foss, Martin M., 1934
  - Foster, Lydia K., 1943
  - Fox, Frederika, 1943
  - Fox, Virginia, 1944
  - Frank, Glenn, 1934
  - Frank, Lawrence, 1942
  - Fraser, Frank W., 1944
  - Freet, H. M., 1935
  - Frey, Leslie L., 1942
  - Freyer, W. N., 1944
  - Friedman, Elisha M., 1944
  - Fritz, W. G., 1942
  - Frost, Wallace, 1943
  - Fryer, E. R., 1943-1944
  - Fuller, Marietta, 1934
  - Fuson, S. D., 1943
  - Galloway, George, 1942-1943
  - Galloway, Lee, 1932
  - Galpin, Perrin, 1932-1944
  - Gardner, George P., 1935-1943
  - Garret, Garet, 1932
  - Garver, R. L., 1943
  - Gasen, R. L., 1943
  - Gates, Moore, 1943
  - Gay, Edwin F., 1929-1933
  - Geist, Raymond H., 1944
  - George, E. B., 1944
  - George, Walter F., 1945
  - Gerhardt, Col. Harrison A., 1944
  - Gerish, E. F., 1932-1934
  - Gerli, Paolino, 1944
  - Gibboney, Carl N., 1944
  - Gibson, Hugh, 1934
  - Gilbert, H. L., Jr., 1944-1946
  - Gildersleeve, Roger, 1942-1946
  - GilFillan, S. C., 1931
  - Gill, Corrington, 1945
  - Gillen, Mrs. Hugh F., 1935
  - Gilpatric, Donald, 1945-1946
  - Ginzberg, Nicola, 1944
  - Glasser, Harold, 1944-1946
  - Gleason, John, 1944
  - Gnudi, Mrs. Dante, 1944
  - Goldstein, J. M., 1945
  - Goodell, Francis, 1932
  - Goodfellow, Col. M. Preston, 1942
  - Gordon, Lincoln, 1942-1943
  - Grady, Henry F., 1944-1945
  - Graf, Gertrude B., 1943
  - Grattan, Della M., 1945
  - Gray, George, 1932
  - Gray, Peter, 1943-1944
  - Grayson, Ferdinand V., 1945
  - Greater Clothing Contractors, 1944
  - Greeff, Rudolf, 1943
  - Greene, Mr. and Mrs. Henry C., 1942-1946
  - Greensfelder, A. P., 1928-1931
  - Gregg, Alan, 1942
  - Gregory, Louise W., 1943
  - Griffis, Col. L. E., 1942
  - Griffith, Ernest S., 1943
  - Griffith, Fay O., 1945
  - Griffiths, Laura, 1944
  - Griggs, Mrs. J. van B., 1943-1944
  - Grosvenor, Gilbert, 1943
  - Grosvenor, Melville, 1943
  - Grover, N. C., 1931
  - Gunn, Selskar M., 1943
  - Gurley, F. J., 1946
  - Haddock, Lt. Col. Geo. H., 1945 (Box 4)
  - Hagemann, Geo. E., 1932
  - Haley, William J., 1944
  - Hall, J. T., 1942
  - Hall, Ray O., 1943
  - Hallowell, Robert C., 1934-1935
  - Halstead, Paul K., 1944
  - Hammond, John Hays, 1923
  - Hanke, L. W., 1943
  - Hankin, Gregory, 1942
  - Hanna, Paul, 1942
  - Hansen, Alvin H., 1942
  - Hansl, Eva, 1942-1944
  - Harr, Luther, 1942
  - Harrison, Shelby, 1934
  - Harvard Alumni Bulletin, 1934
  - Harvard Trust Co., 1944
  - Haskell, Gen. William N., 1943-1944
  - Hawke, W. E., 1932-1933
  - Hawkins, Harry, 1942
  - Hayes, William, 1942-1946
  - Heck, Mrs. L. D., 1945
  - Hein, Lionel, 1945
  - Heizer, J., 1944
  - Helmer, Mrs. Borden, 1943
  - Helmer, Burd, 1943
  - Hendrickson, Roy F., 1944
  - Henry, Philip W., 1942
  - Hensel, Struve H., 1945
  - Herter, Christian, 1945
  - Herwitz, Harry K., 1943-1944
  - Hicks, Granville, 1935
  - Hill, F. E., 1944
  - Hill, T. Arnold, 1932
  - Hilldring, Maj. Gen. J. H., 1944-1946
  - Hinricks, A. F., 1942-1946
  - Hinshaw, David, 1942-1943
  - Hobson, Asher, 1943
  - Hodges, Margaret B., 1934
  - Hofstadter, Richard, 1943-1944
  - Holm, Marion, 1944
  - Holmes, Oliver W., 1944
  - Holstein, Elwood, 1945
  - Hooper, H. O., 1944-1945
  - Hoover, President Herbert, 1919-1933
  - Hoover Institution, 1933-1934
  - Hopgood, Jim, 1941
  - Howard, M. S., 1931
  - Huisking, Charles, 1944
  - Hull, Cordell, 1944
  - Hunt, Edward E., 1944
  - Hunt, Mrs. Frederick G., 1943
  - Hunt, Juliet D., 1935
  - Hunt, Laura S., 1934-1935
  - Hurlbutt, Isabelle B., 1942
  - Hyland, Joseph A., 1929
  - Isrin-Olwei Company, 1944
  - Italian Drugs Importing Company, 1945
  - Italo-American Radio Review, 1944
  - Jackling, Roger W., 1945
  - Jaffa, Alma, 1945
  - James, Concha Romero, 1942
  - James H. Rhodes and Company, 1944
  - James, John H., 1943-1944
  - Jamieson, Mabel A., 1943
  - Johnson, Alvin, 1942
  - Jones, Lt. Col. Harry P. 1944-1945
  - Jones, John W., 1944
  - Jones, Norman G., 1944
  - Jostes, Charles A., 1946
  - Justin, Joel D., 1944
  - Kadell, Harry, 1943
  - Kahn, Herman, 1942
  - Karl, William A., n.d.
  - Kaufman, H. M., 1942-1943
  - Keeny, S. M., 1943-1945
  - Keller, Joseph, 1944-1945
  - Kent, Sherman, 1945
  - Keppel, Frederick, 1943
  - Kerlin, Malcolm, 1943
  - Kerno, Ivan, 1945
  - Key, David, 1946
  - Kilday, Paul J., 1944
  - King, Clarence, 1942-1944
  - Kinney, Edward M., 1944
  - Kiplinger, Willard M., 1937-1943
  - Kirk, Alexander, 1945
  - Knauth, Arnold W., 1943
  - Knauth, Oswald, 1942-1944
  - Knebel, G. M., 1942
  - Kreps, Theodore, 1942-1943
  - Krould, H. J., n.d.
  - Kubowitzki, A. Leon, 1944
  - Kugel, Leonard, 1944-1945
  - Kuznets, Simon, 1931
  - Labouisse, Henry, 1945
  - Laidler, Harry, 1942
  - Land, Vice Adm., E. S., 1945
  - Lane, Mortimer, 1944
  - Larom, Irving H., 1943
  - Latimer, Lt. Col., Claude A., 1945
  - Latimer, Murray, 1943-1946
  - Laughlin, Gerald F., 1944
  - Lawler, J. J., 1945
  - Lee, Julie, 1944
  - Leffingwell, W. H., 1934
  - Lehman, Herbert H., 1943-1946
  - Leiserson, William, 1944
  - Lemmon, Walter, 1943-1944
  - Leven, Maurice, 1942
  - Levy, Charles, 1944 (Box 5)
  - Lewison, Samuel A., 1944
  - Library of Congress, 1933
  - Lincoln, Leroy A., 1944
  - Lindsay, Anatol, 1944
  - Lippman, Walter, 1935
  - Livingston, J. A., 1944
  - Lloyd, E. N. H., 1943
  - Loeb, Harold, 1942
  - Lopez, Elsa, 1944
  - Lorwin, Lewis L., 1946
  - Loveday, Alexander, 1942
  - Lowe, Adolph, 1942
  - Lubell, Samuel, 1942
  - Lucas, D. B., 1942
  - Lucas, Lt. Col. Otis P., 1943
  - Luchini, James, 1943
  - Lund, J. W., 1942
  - Lund, John, 1942
  - Lund, Marquard H., 1942
  - Luzardo, Rodolfo, 1942-1943
  - Luzzatto, Bruno, 1944-1946
  - Lynch, R. J., 1945
  - Mabrito, van Doale, 1944
  - MacBride, Burt, 1943
  - McCabe, Thomas B., 1945
  - McCamy, James L., 1946
  - McCarter, R. D., 1944
  - McCarthy, John T., 1943
  - McClenahan, Howard, 1928
  - McCloy, John J., 1945
  - McColl, Esten, 1942
  - McCown, Albert, 1942
  - McDonough, C., 1944
  - McFarling, J. R., 1935
  - McGhee, George, 1943
  - McGraw Hill Book Company, Inc., 1929-1934
  - Machold, W. M., 1942
  - McKewen, Sherlock, 1945
  - McKinley, Gen. E. B., 1945
  - McMullin, Dave, n.d.
  - Madden, James L., 1944
  - Maffry, August, 1945-1946
  - Magnusson, Leifur, 1943
  - Mahoney, Joseph C., 1944
  - Mallery, Otto T., 1936-1941
  - Mann, Elizabeth, 1943
  - Maphis, Alan, 1943
  - Marchisio, Juvenal, 1944-1946
  - Markham, Gen. E. M., 1944
  - Marquis, J. Clyde, 1943
  - Marshall, Gen. George C., 1944
  - Marshall, Lee, 1943
  - Martin, C. E., Jr., 1945
  - Martin, Robert F., 1942
  - Martin, William McC., Jr., 1946
  - Martinlizzi, Leo, 1944
  - Marvin, Donald M., 1942-1943
  - Matthews, John, 1943
  - Mattioli, Raffaele, 1945
  - Maurice, Frank J., 1944
  - Mayer, Raymond C., 1934
  - Mayword, L. A., 1944
  - Mead, James M., 1945
  - Meier, H., 1934
  - Menshikov, M., 1944
  - Merriam, Charles E., 1943
  - Merrill, M. C., 1942
  - Merritt, James M., 1945
  - Merz, Charles, 1944
  - Meyer, Eugene, 1930
  - Meyers, James F., 1944
  - Millard, J. W., 1942-1943
  - Miller, Adolph C., 1942
  - Miller, Bernice, 1944
  - Miller, Clayton, 1944
  - Miller, James C., 1944
  - Millis, H. A., 1930-1944
  - Mills, Frederick C., 1931-1932
  - Milton, George Fort., 1942-1946
  - Minor, Clark H., 1944
  - Mitchell, H. S., 1943
  - Mitchell, Sidney, 1944
  - Mitchell, Walter, Jr., 1942
  - Mitchell, Wesley C., 1931-1933
  - Moffett, Guy, 1942
  - Moore, William C., 1944
  - Morawetz, Otto, 1945
  - More, G. R., 1945
  - Morely, F. V., 1942
  - Morris, Henry Curtis, 1942
  - Morrison, C. E., Jr., 1944
  - Morse, Walter C. B., 1944
  - Mote, John R., 1942
  - Muller, Charles, G., 1943
  - Mulliken, Otis, 1944
  - Munn, John R., 1942
  - Murphey, G. D., 1945
  - Murphy, Mallie J., 1934
  - Murray, Henry A., 1943
  - Murray, Mrs. Leslie, 1944
  - Murtagh, Lt. Col. John M., 1945-1946
  - Myers, Paul, 1945
  - Myhre, C. B., 1945
  - Nation, 1921-1923 (Box 6)
  - National Catholic Welfare Conference, 1944
  - National Fuels Company, 1945
  - Nelson, Donald M., 1944
  - Nicotri, Franco, 1945
  - Noble, William H., 1942
  - Nolan, Louis C., 1943
  - Noland, Louis, 1944
  - O'Boyle, Rt. Rev. Monsignor P. A., 1944
  - Odum, Howard, 1934
  - O'Dwyer, Brig., Gen. William, 1944-1946
  - Office of the Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1943
  - Ogburn, W. F., 1934
  - Ogden, William L., 1942
  - Ohio Edison Company, 1935
  - Ohrbach, Mrs. Jerome, 1944
  - Olds, Leland, 1942
  - Ortona, Egidio, 1945-1946
  - Osborne, Lithgow, 1943
  - Osborne, Maurice, 1943
  - Pace, Anderson, 1942
  - Pace, Antonio, 1945
  - Pacific Industrial Corporation, 1944
  - Page, W. H., n.d.
  - Palmer, Arthur E., 1944
  - Pappas, Thomas A., 1944
  - Paredi, John, 1944
  - Parisius, Herbert W., 1942-1946
  - Parran, Thomas, 1942
  - Pasch, J., 1946
  - Passerini, Lena, 1944
  - Paul, Arthur, 1945-1946
  - Pavia, Enrico L., 1945
  - Persons, W. Frank, 1942
  - Phelps, Reginald H., 1943
  - Phelps, Vernon L., 1944
  - Pickering, Gwendoline, 1928
  - Piggot, C. S., 1942
  - Place, David E., 1944
  - Poland, W. B., 1943
  - Poletti, Charles, 1945-1946
  - Potts, George, 1944
  - Poynter, Nelson T., n.d.
  - Preston, Jean I., 1943
  - Previtali, John, 1944-1945
  - Quaremba, John, 1944
  - Rapp, C. H., 1945
  - Rayner, Charles, 1943
  - Reed, Maj. F. C., 1942
  - Reid, T. Roy, 1942
  - Resnik, Reuben B., 1943
  - Ricci, Thomas A., 1944
  - Richards, Col. Artherton, 1942
  - Richardson, Mrs. Inez, 1933-1934
  - Richey, Lawrence, 1934
  - Richie, A. E., 1942
  - Richter, J. H., 1945-1946
  - Rickard, Edgar, 1933-1935
  - Robbins, Douglas, 1943
  - Robbins, William, 1942-1943
  - Roberts, M. A., 1934
  - Robinson, J., 1944
  - Rockefeller Foundation, 1927-1934
  - Rockwell, Berry, 1944
  - Roessle, R. L. B., 1942-1944
  - Rogers, James G., 1942
  - Rogers, Walter S., 1944-1945
  - Romano, Tullio, 1944
  - Roncallo, I. F., 1945
  - Roseman, Alvin, 1944
  - Rosenman, Samuel I., 1945
  - Rosenthal, Morris, 1945
  - Roth, Eleanor E., 1944
  - Rounds, Harold E., 1944
  - Russell, Francis, 1945
  - Rutledge, Wiley B., 1943
  - Ryan, Carson, 1942
  - Ryan, F. W., 1942
  - Ryan, Philip, 1944-1946
  - Sacerdoti, Cesare, 1945-1946
  - Sackett, R. L., 1944
  - Salter, Sir and Mme. Arthur, 1944
  - Sampson, Richard H., 1944
  - Sandvoss, H. G., 1942
  - Santillana, G., 1944
  - Sard, Edward L., 1946
  - Sarjeant, Jean J., 1942
  - Saxon, Glenn, 1936-1938
  - Sayler, C. O., 1945
  - Sayre, Francis B., 1943
  - Scaretti, Enrico, 1945
  - Schachtman, Miss, 1942
  - Scharff, Maurice, 1944
  - Scheuer, Sidney H., 1944-1945
  - Schmidt, Emerson P., 1943
  - Schmidt, Orvis A., 1944
  - Schroeder, W. C., 1944
  - Schultz, T. W., 1942-1943
  - Seabury, George T., 1944
  - Seaman, George, 1943
  - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1942
  - Seidelmann, Ernst, 1944
  - Seymour, Charles, 1933
  - Seymour, Edward P., 1944
  - Shaler, Millard K., 1934
  - Shaw, Arch W., 1929-1942 (Box 7)
  - Shaw, John I., 1943
  - Shepherd, Eugenia, 1945
  - Sheppard, S. S., 1946
  - Shingler, Brig., Gen. D. C., 1945
  - Shipley, Ruth B., 1945
  - Shotwell, James T., 1933
  - Sibley, Hiram, 1943-1946
  - Sigillito, Anthony, 1944
  - Sills, K. C. M., 1944
  - Slentz, Helen, 1942
  - Slettery, Harry, 1942
  - Slichter, Sumner H., 1942-1944
  - Smith, J. Russell, 1933-1943
  - Smith, L. M. C., 1943-1944
  - Smith, R. K., n.d.
  - Sozzie, E. L., 1944-1945
  - Spalding, Albert, 1945
  - Spencer, DeForest, 1944
  - Spitzer, H., 1943
  - Spofford, Brig., Gen., Charles, 1944-1945
  - Stanley, Edward, n.d. (Box 8)
  - Steele, George S., 1944
  - Stefansson, Mrs. V., 1944
  - Stettinius, E. R., Jr., 1943
  - Stevenson, Adlai, 1943
  - Stewart, Charles L., 1944
  - Stewart, Stella, 1942
  - Stillwell, J. A., 1944-1946
  - Stimson, Julia C., 1937
  - Stinebower, Leroy D., 1944
  - Stockton, Gilchrist, 1944
  - Stone, N. I., 1942
  - Stratton, William C., 1944
  - Stritch, Samuel A., 1946
  - Struthers, Lester B., 1938
  - Stuart, John, 1934
  - Sturges, Wesley A., 1944
  - Sturzo, Don Luigi, 1944-1945
  - Sullivan, A. H., 1945
  - Sullivan, Gael, 1945-1946
  - Surface, Frank M., 1943-1944
  - Swanson, Edward B., 1942
  - Synan, Edward M., 1943
  - Szymczak, M. S., 1943
  - Tamagna, Frank M., 1945-1946
  - Tarchiani, Alberto, 1945-1946
  - Tarver, Malcolm C., 1945
  - Taylor, Amos, 1943
  - Taylor, Ann, 1942
  - Taylor, Horace, 1934
  - Taylor, James S., 1934
  - Taylor, M. H., 1944
  - Taylor, Myron C., 1946
  - Taylor, Thomas R., 1934
  - Tead, Ordway, 1942-1943
  - Tees, Jack M., 1944
  - Texas and Pacific Railway Company, 1945
  - Thibodeaux, Col. B. H., 1944
  - Thomas, M., 1942
  - Thompson, Sanford E., 1942-1946
  - Thomson, Charles M., 1942
  - Thorne, Florence, 1934-1942
  - Tirana, Rifat, 1943-1946
  - Tobin, Maurice C., 1944
  - Townsend, Mrs. H. H., 1945
  - Treasury Procurement Division, 1945
  - Treutle, Peter G., 1944-1946